<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Welcome to CSC 111</title>
    <link>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Welcome to CSC 111</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial 1: Getting Started with Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/installation/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, we will walk you through the installation of Visual Studio Code.
Step 1. Install Visual Studio Code Goto VS Code releases, download the appropriate version for your os and archietecture.
 Download Windows if your os is Windows 8, 10, 11 Download Mac if your os is macOX 10.11+  Open the installer you just download, it will install Visual Studio Code for you by default. After installation finish, you will find the VS Code Application on your Desktop/Lauchpad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial 2: Download and Install Python (macOS)</title>
      <link>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/pythoninstall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/pythoninstall/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, you will learn how to download and install Python on macOS.
Step 1: Check Python First step we need to check if Python is already installed on your laptop. If you are working on a cluster, skip this step, we have taken care of everything.
We can check it via terminal. First, on your VS Code, click Terminal &amp;gt; New Terminal from top menu to open a new terminal: Below red box is the new terminal we just opened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial 2: Download and Install Python (Windows)</title>
      <link>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/installwindows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/installwindows/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, you will learn how to download and install Python on Windows.
Step 1: Download Python Quick Link: click HERE to download Python 3.10.5 for Windows(64-bit)
Or, visit Python Homepage python.org, Downloads &amp;gt; Windows to visit the download page for Windows: Step 2: Install Python Launch python-3.10.5-amd64.exe that you just downloaded in Step 1.
Click Next to start installation: Until the last step: When the installation is done, it will lauch VS Code automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial 3: Set up Python Environment (macOS)</title>
      <link>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/pythonenv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/pythonenv/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, you will set up a Python environment in Visual Studio Code. The Microsoft Python extension will be introduced, through using the Python extension, you make VS Code into a great lightweight Python IDE.
Step 1: Install the Python Extension Let&amp;rsquo;s open VS Code.
First, you click the Extension button on the left menu to open the Visual Studio Marketplace.
In the Marketplace, search Python.
You will see tons of Python-related extensions, here we want to install the one developed by Microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial 3: Set up Python Environment (Windows)</title>
      <link>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/envwindows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/envwindows/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, you will set up a Python environment in Visual Studio Code. The Microsoft Python extension will be introduced, through using the Python extension, you make VS Code into a great lightweight Python IDE.
Step 1: Install the Python Extension Let&amp;rsquo;s open VS Code.
First, you click the Extension button on the left menu to open the Visual Studio Marketplace.
In the Marketplace, search Python.
You will see tons of Python-related extensions, here we want to install the one developed by Microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial 4: Run Python Hello World</title>
      <link>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/pythonhelloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/pythonhelloworld/</guid>
      <description>Step 1: Create Python Hello World Source Code File Remember the step 4 in Tutorial 1, how we open a folder. By starting VS Code in a folder, that folder becomes your workspace.
Here we create a new foler under Desktop: We name the folder as hello and open it (the hello folder is your workplace): Then we select New File button create a new file in hello folder, name it hello.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial 5: Jupyter Notebooks on VS Code</title>
      <link>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/jupyter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/jupyter/</guid>
      <description>Jupyter Notebooks is an open-source project that combines Markdown text and executable Python source code on one canvas.
In Tutorial 3 we lhave earn how to set up Python enviroment. Once the appropriate environment is activated, we can create and open a Jupyter Notebook.
Step 1: Install Jupyter Notebook Extension Search Jupyter in extension marketplace:
Make sure it is developed by Microsoft, install it. Step 2: Create or Open a Jupyter Notebook Open the Command Palete in top menu View &amp;gt; Command Palette:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial 6: Install and Use Packages</title>
      <link>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/packageinstall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://JialiangTan.github.io/vscodetutorial/post/packageinstall/</guid>
      <description>In Python, packages are how you obtain any number of useful code libraries, typically from the Python Package Index (PyPI). Here we show an example that&amp;rsquo;s a little more complicated, where you use the matplotlib and numpy packages to create a graphical plot as is commonly done with data science.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s create a new file called plot.py, and paste in the following source code:
import matplotlib.pyplot as plt import numpy as np x = np.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
